[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie won the awards for Best Sound, Best Editing, Best Sound Effects Editing and Best Visual Effects at the 72nd Academy Awards 2000?", "correct_answer": "The Matrix", "incorrect_answers": ["Star Wars: Episode I The Phantom Menace", "The Mummy", "Stuart Little"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the scale that is used to rate the intensity of tornadoes?", "correct_answer": "Fujita scale", "incorrect_answers": ["Dmitriev scale", "Richter scale", "Saccitoni scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animals are the Yellow jackets, the scavenging and predatory animals belonging to the genera Vespula and Dolichovespula?", "correct_answer": "Wasps", "incorrect_answers": ["Flies", "All of these", "Bees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies directed by Alfred Hitchcock tells the true story of a man who was wrongly accused of a crime?", "correct_answer": "The Wrong Man", "incorrect_answers": ["To Catch a Thief", "The Man Who Knew Too Much", "I Confess"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the French academic dress system, what academic field is symbolized by the redcurrant color -- an extremely red shade of pink?", "correct_answer": "Medicine", "incorrect_answers": ["Theology", "Law", "Arts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of the following are common causes of elevated liver enzymes EXCEPT which one?", "correct_answer": "Cholelithiasis", "incorrect_answers": ["HMG Co-enzyme-A Reductase Inhibitors", "Alcohol abuse", "Fatty Liver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular actress made a cameo appearance in the 1992 movie The Player, starring Whoopi Goldberg?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Julia Roberts", "Cher", "Susan Sarandon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Slovakia and Slovenia joined the European Union on the same day (May 1, 2004). Which of them was first to accept the euro currency?", "correct_answer": "Slovenia", "incorrect_answers": ["None of them has accepted the EURO currency.", "Both did on the day of their accession to the EU.", "Slovakia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these singers was not one of the original Supremes?", "correct_answer": "Cindy Birdsong", "incorrect_answers": ["Florence Ballard", "Diana Ross", "Mary Wilson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A man shoots his wife. Then he holds her underwater for 5-10 minutes. Then he hangs her. 30 minutes later they go out to dinner at a 5-star restaurant. How is this possible?", "correct_answer": "He is a photographer", "incorrect_answers": ["none of these", "He brings her back to life.", "He remarries."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which card game, invented by British poet Sir John Suckling, is scored with a peg board?", "correct_answer": "Cribbage", "incorrect_answers": ["Piquet", "Canasta", "Euchre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Jett, George Lucas son, play in Episode III:  Revenge of the Sith?", "correct_answer": "Zett Jukassa", "incorrect_answers": ["a clone trooper", "General Grievous", "Nute Gunray"]}]